Hari Sharma fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Publication and exhibition files, 1951 - 2006; F-251-5; 88 cm of textual records
  - Socio-political writings, 1960 - 2006; F-251-5-3; 25 cm of textual records
    - India Today: Indian Canadians have had a long history of fighting political and cultural discrimination, 1999; F-251-5-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 251-66)
    - The South Asian Bomb: Reality and Illusion, 1999; F-251-5-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 251-66)
    - American Imperialism and Nuclear Carrot, 2006; F-251-5-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 251-66)
    - Booklets on issues of peace and security: Indo-US Nuclear Deal, [ca 2006]; F-251-5-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 251-66)
    - Critical Perspecties on China's Economic Transformation, 2006; F-251-5-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 251-66)
    - Introduction: Some Reflections on "China and Socialism Roundtable", 2006; F-251-5-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 251-66)
- Special media records, 1970 - 2006; F-251-6; 47 moving images
  Series consists of non-textual records (special media) made and received by Hari Sharma and maintained separately from the textual files. Records include photographs, audio-visual recordings, and audio recordings.
  The series was established by the SFU Archives to bring together all non-textual materials kept apart from the textal records by Hari Sharma. Sub-series were established on the basis of media, format, or event.
  Moving images; Sound recordings; Photographic materials
  No further accruals are expected.
  As stipulated by Archives policy, some files may be restricted or be given a pending review access status due to the following:
  In the case of special media, the archivist will need to evaluate the physical condition of records to determine the proper conservation treatment for each type of media. Restrictions might apply if playback would cause further deterioration or if no other copies of the record exist. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Sound and moving images collection, 1980 - 2005; F-251-6-1; Physical description: includes 47 VHS videocassettes, 177 audio cassettes, 25 Hi8 videocassettes
    Sub-series includes sound and moving image material created by or relating to Hari Sharma's personal and academic life.
    Moving images; Sound recordings
    - Biographical and personal videos, 1984 - [ca 2000]; F-251-6-1-0-1
      Textual records; Moving images
      - SFU: Retirement party, 1999; F-251-6-1-0-1-1 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4101)
        Moving images
      - Photo-poetry show at SFU Bennett Gallery, 1999; F-251-6-1-0-1-2 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4102)
      - Shalini: Kathak; Dalit meeting (99/05/10), 1999; F-251-6-1-0-1-3 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4103)
      - Sailani Sharma Kathak (Ganga: Shiv K. Sharma, Shrasti: Haripra Chaurasia), 1996 - 1999; F-251-6-1-0-1-4 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4104, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4105, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4106)
      - H. Sharma play, 1984; F-251-6-1-0-1-5 (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-4149, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-4150)
    - South Asian community activism and cultural event videos, [ca 1991] - [ca 2002]; F-251-6-1-0-2
      - SANSAD Forum on Gujarat Genocide (July 20/2002), F-251-6-1-0-2-1 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4107)
      - South Asia Diaspora, INSAF Conference Vancouver (Aug. 11, 2001), F-251-6-1-0-2-2 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4108)
      - NRISAD: The 50th Year, Aug. 14, 1997, F-251-6-1-0-2-3 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4109, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4110)
      - NRISAD - India Mela: Opening ceremony (July 23,1994), F-251-6-1-0-2-4 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4111)
      - NRISAD Dinner with Shabana Azmi (Sept. 16, 1994), F-251-6-1-0-2-5 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4112)
      - NRISAD pgm: The 50th Year, Aug 14 / 1997 (master tape 1), F-251-6-1-0-2-6 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4395)
      - NRISAD pgm: The 50th Year, Aug 14 / 1997 (master tape 2), F-251-6-1-0-2-7 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4396)
      - P. Sainath: NRISAD public lecture, May 18 / 1997, F-251-6-1-0-2-8 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4397)
      - NRISAD Youth Team, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-2-9 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4398)
      - Axis of Goodwill, part 1, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-2-10 (Videocassette: hi8 (mp, or metal particle) OBJ-4407)
        Multi-media; Moving images
      - Axis of Goodwill, part 2, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-2-11 (Videocassette: hi8 (mp, or metal particle) OBJ-4408)
    - First Nations cultural education and exchange videos, [ca 1988] - [ca 1998]; F-251-6-1-0-3
      - Secwepemc Cultural Education Society: Our University then and now, [ca 1998]; F-251-6-1-0-3-1 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4113)
      - Framing the Issues, [199-?]; F-251-6-1-0-3-2 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4114)
      - No 'XYA' (Our Footprints), 1988, Headlines Theatre, [ca 1988]; F-251-6-1-0-3-3 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4115)
      - SFU Kamloops convocation, 1994 - [ca 1994]; F-251-6-1-0-3-4 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4116)
      - Ros (95 Meares), [199-]; F-251-6-1-0-3-5 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4117)
      - Whispering Pine, Nov 18 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-6 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4383)
      - Percy Casper (Bonaparte), Dec 1 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-7 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4384)
      - Agnes Snow in SCES / SFU classroom, Nov 3 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-8 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4385)
      - Canoe Creek, Oct 18 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-9 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4386)
      - SCES Banquet (Thompson Highway), Feb 15 / 1996, F-251-6-1-0-3-10 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4387)
      - Ron Jules, Adams Lake, Oct 21 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-11 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4388)
      - Kamloops pow wow, etc; Aug 19-20 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-12 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4389)
      - Canoe Creek II, Oct 18 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-13 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4390)
      - Chase / Adams Lake Reserve, #4, Oct 21 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-14 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4391)
      - Nathan Mathew, Oct 27 / 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-15 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4392)
      - Shuswap, Vidette Lake, Devali, 1995, F-251-6-1-0-3-16 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4393)
    - Research and conference videos, [ca 1987] - [ca 2004]; F-251-6-1-0-4
      - Dr. Rajni Kothari Speaks (interview by Hari Sharma), 1987; F-251-6-1-0-4-1 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4118)
      - No Small Matter, A video on family violence in Punjabi, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-4-2 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4119)
      - Meera Dewar: This is our home, eh?, [199-?]; F-251-6-1-0-4-3 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4120)
      - Anhad Garje [artists against communalism, collective art promoting communal harmony in the wake of the Babri Masjid destruction], [ca 1993]; F-251-6-1-0-4-4 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4121, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4122)
      - Tom Berger on Narbada Dam interview, Vancouver, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-4-5 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4124)
      - Cross Cultural with Manpreet Grewal (host), [ca 1994]; F-251-6-1-0-4-6 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4125)
      - Ethnic Preservation, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-4-7 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4123)
      - Identity-based oppression of India, Guru Ravidas Youth Association, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-4-8 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4126)
      - Dr. Ambedkar's books, 1996; F-251-6-1-0-4-9 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4127)
      - No to APEC conference, 1997; F-251-6-1-0-4-10 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4128)
      - Mahesh Dattani's Final Solutions, 1997; F-251-6-1-0-4-11 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4129, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4130)
      - Nuclear Terror in an Economy of Scarcity, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-4-12 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4131, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4132, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4133)
      - BC Punjab Cultural Foundation, 1999; F-251-6-1-0-4-13 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4134)
      - A Day Will Come, 2000; F-251-6-1-0-4-14 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4135)
      - Deconstructing Supper, 2001; F-251-6-1-0-4-15 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4136)
      - Paperny Films: Audrey Mehlar with Hari Sharma for "ToLove, Honour, & Obey", 2001; F-251-6-1-0-4-16 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4137)
      - Dr. Hari Sharma at the UNC Great Decisions Program, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-4-17 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4138)
      - Douglas College Diversity Week 2002, Dr. Sunera Thobani: A Guest Lecture, F-251-6-1-0-4-18 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4139)
      - Gujarat Forum, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-4-19 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4140)
      - When Beasts Were Let Lose: Genocide in Gujarat and the Relief Work Ahead, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-4-20 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4141)
      - Dr. Jaiashankar, NJ, July 21, 2002, F-251-6-1-0-4-21 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4142)
      - A Tribe of His Own: The Journalism of P. Sainath, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-4-22 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4143)
      - MSK Productions: Dehra Dun Farmers on Navdanya Farm, 2002; F-251-6-1-0-4-23 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4144)
      - Hari Sharma at the "Laws, Labels & Liberation" conference in Montreal, 2004; F-251-6-1-0-4-24 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4145)
      - Final Solution by Rakesh Sharma, 2004; F-251-6-1-0-4-25 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4146)
      - National Film Board of Canada, Bhopal: The Search for Justice, [ca 2004]; F-251-6-1-0-4-26 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-4147)
      - Tape II: Press Club Delhi / Jaipur, March 4 / 1998, F-251-6-1-0-4-27 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4399)
      - Tape III: Assam Majha Dabri Village, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-4-28 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4400)
      - Tape IV: R. Yadava - A. Dube / Tanvir Family / Manesh - Sameer, etc., 1998; F-251-6-1-0-4-29 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4401)
      - Tape V: Jaijee / A. Bains / Imtiaz Ahmad, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-4-30 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4402)
      - Tape VI: Imtiaz Ahmad (continued) / Manlayam S. Yadavi, etc., 1998; F-251-6-1-0-4-31 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4403)
      - Tape VII: India 1998 (Sonal / Ashim / KN Panikkar / Birthday party), F-251-6-1-4-0-32 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4404)
      - Tape VIII: Patna, Dr. R.S Sharma / Barabanki / Rajni Kothari / Delhi streets and bomb, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-4-33 (Videocassette: hi8 (metal mp) OBJ-4405)
      - Tape IX: Somonto Banerjee / Streets and Bomb / Shahabuddin, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-4-34 (Videocassette: hi8 (mp) OBJ-4406)
    - Shuswap interviews, 1990 - 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5
      Sound recordings; Moving images
      - Ron Ignace: Jan 13/90, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4410)
        Sound recordings
      - Ron Ignace: Jan 13/90; last part of tape 1, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4411)
      - Ron Ignace: Jan 27/90; tape IIa, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4412)
      - Ron Ignace: Jan 27/90; tape 2, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4413)
      - Eddy Jules: Mar 18/90; tape I, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4414)
      - Eddy Jules: Mar 18/90; tape IIa, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-4415)
      - Terry Deneault: May 5/90; tape I, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-4416)
      - Terry Deneault: May 5/90; tape IIa, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-4417)
      - Mel Seymour, Kamloops Band: June 2/90, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-4418)
      - Whispering Pine, Rick LeBourdais: June 10/90; tape Ia, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-4419)
      - LeBourdais, tape II, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-4420)
      - Richard Jules, Kamloops Indian Band: Oct 6/90; tape I, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-4421)
      - Richard Jules, Kamloops Indian Band: Oct 6/90; tape 2, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-4422)
      - Nellie Taylor: Oct 20/90, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-4423)
      - Nellie Taylor: Oct 20/90, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-4424)
      - Mel Seymour: June 12/90, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-5-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-4425)
      - Robert Manuel: April 21/91, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-5-17 (Cassette box OBJ-4426)
      - Robert Manuel, tape II: April 27/91, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-5-18 (Cassette box OBJ-4427)
      - Manny Jules (Kamloops Band): Oct 11/91, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-5-19 (Cassette box OBJ-4428)
      - Manny Jules (Kamloops Band), tape II: Oct 11/91, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-5-20 (Cassette box OBJ-4429)
      - Terry Denault (Skeetchesen): Oct 13/91, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-5-21 (Cassette box OBJ-4430)
      - Terry Denault (Skeetchesen): Oct 13/91, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-5-22 (Cassette box OBJ-4431)
      - Eddy Jules (Skeetchesen): Oct 31/91, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-5-23 (Cassette box OBJ-4432)
      - Ron Ignace: Feb 2/92; tape IV, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-5-24 (Cassette box OBJ-4433)
      - Ron Ignace: Feb 2/92; tape IV (copy), 1992; F-251-6-1-0-5-25 (Cassette box OBJ-4434)
      - Ron Ignace: Feb 2/92; tape V (copy), 1992; F-251-6-1-0-5-26 (Cassette box OBJ-4435)
      - Ron Ignace: Feb 2/92; tape V, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-5-27 (Cassette box OBJ-4436)
      - Chief Nathan Mathews (North Thompson): Aug 5/92, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-5-28 (Cassette box OBJ-4437)
      - Nathan Mathews (North Thompson): Aug 5/92; tape I, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-5-29 (Cassette box OBJ-4438)
      - Louella Jules: April 21/93; tape I, 1993; F-251-6-1-0-5-30 (Cassette box OBJ-4439)
      - Louella Jules: April 21/93; tape II, 1993; F-251-6-1-0-5-31 (Cassette box OBJ-4440)
      - John Jules (Kamloops): April 25/93; tape I, 1993; F-251-6-1-0-5-32 (Cassette box OBJ-4441)
      - John Jules (Kamloops): April 25/93, 1993; F-251-6-1-0-5-33 (Cassette box OBJ-4442)
      - Dorothy Jepp and Ramona Holota: July 15/93, 1993; F-251-6-1-0-5-34 (Cassette box OBJ-4443)
      - Dorothy Jepp and Ramona Holota: July 15/93; tape II, 1993; F-251-6-1-0-5-35 (Cassette box OBJ-4444)
      - Richard Jules (Kamloops): Jan 27/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-36 (Cassette box OBJ-4445)
      - Louisa Celesta: April 26/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-37 (Cassette box OBJ-4446)
      - R. Casimir (Kamloops Band): April 27/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-38 (Cassette box OBJ-4447)
      - Bernice Manuel (grad): April 27/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-39 (Audio cassette OBJ-4448)
      - Gladys Baptiste: April 29/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-40 (Audio cassette OBJ-4449)
      - Verna Billy (Kamloops): April 29/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-41 (Audio cassette OBJ-4450)
      - Natalie Simkin: April 29/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-42 (Audio cassette OBJ-4451)
      - Donna Dillman: April 29/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-43 (Audio cassette OBJ-4452)
      - Verna Billy: April 29/94; tape I, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-44 (Audio cassette OBJ-4453)
      - Verna Billy: April 29/94; tape II, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-45 (Audio cassette OBJ-4454)
      - Lister Sinclair (host of IDEAS profiling Chief George Manuel): May 3/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-46 (Audio cassette OBJ-4455)
      - Chief Feli Arnouse (Little Shuswap): June 13/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-47 (Audio cassette OBJ-4456)
      - Little Shuswap: Chief Felix Arnouse: June 13/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-48 (Audio cassette OBJ-4457)
      - Chief Cindy Williams: Oct 13/94; tape I, Vancouver, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-49 (Audio cassette OBJ-4458)
      - Chief Cindy Williams: Oct 13/94; tape II, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-50 (Audio cassette OBJ-4459)
      - Chief Cindy Williams: Oct 13/94; tape III, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-51 (Audio cassette OBJ-4460)
      - Chief Terry Porter (Bonaparte): Oct 28/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-52 (Audio cassette OBJ-4461)
      - Gerald Etienne: Oct 27/94, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-53 (Audio cassette OBJ-4462)
      - G. Etienne: Oct 27/94; tape II, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-54 (Audio cassette OBJ-4463)
      - G. Etienne: Oct 27/94; tape III, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-5-55 (Audio cassette OBJ-4464)
      - Allan Casimir: March 3/95; tape I, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-56 (Audio cassette OBJ-4465)
      - Allan Casimir: March 3/95; tape II, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-57 (Audio cassette OBJ-4466)
      - Sonal: Norma Scheffer, INUCEP Coordinator: March 17/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-58 (Audio cassette OBJ-4467)
      - Sonal: First few minutes (own observations) and Verna Billy: March 14/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-59 (Audio cassette OBJ-4468)
      - Sonal: Continuing with Verna Billy: March 14/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-60 (Audio cassette OBJ-4469)
      - Sonal: Daniel, INUCEP student: April 6/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-61 (Audio cassette OBJ-4470)
      - Sonal: Aveline (elder-school teacher) and Fred Fortier: April 13/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-62 (Audio cassette OBJ-4471)
      - Clarence Jules: April 6/95; tape I, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-63 (Audio cassette OBJ-4472)
      - Clarence Jules: April 6/95; tape II, 1995; F--251-6-1-0-5-64 (Audio cassette OBJ-4473)
      - Sonal: Mona Jules (of North Thompson): April 6/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-65 (Audio cassette OBJ-4474)
      - Arnold Baptiste (North Thompson): April 8/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-66 (Audio cassette OBJ-4475)
      - Arnold Baptiste (North Thompson): April 8/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-67 (Audio cassette OBJ-4476)
      - Sonal: Don Ignace (Skeetchesen Band): April 10/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-68 (Audio cassette OBJ-4477)
      - Sonal: Roundtable presentation by Fred Fortier, Salmon Arms: April 13/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-69 (Audio cassette OBJ-4478)
      - Sonal: Fred Fortier (Salmon Arms): April 13/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-70 (Audio cassette OBJ-4479)
      - Ron/MBI: Oct 7/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-71 (Audio cassette OBJ-4480)
      - William & Evelyn Sargent, Canoe Creek: Oct 18/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-72 (Audio cassette OBJ-4481)
      - Mrs. Sargent, Canoe Creek: Oct 19/95, F-251-6-1-0-5-73 (Audio cassette OBJ-4482)
      - David Archie, Administrator, Canoe Creek: Oct 19/95, F-251-6-1-0-5-74 (Audio cassette OBJ-4483)
      - Ron Jules, Adams Lake: Oct 21/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-75 (Audio cassette OBJ-4484)
      - Ron Jules, Adams Lake: Oct 21/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-76 (Audio cassette OBJ-4485)
      - Chief Nathan Mathew (North Thompson): Oct 27/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-77 (Audio cassette OBJ-4486)
      - Chief Nathan Mathew: Oct 27/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-78 (Audio cassette OBJ-4487)
      - Agnes Snow (Canoe Creek) talking to SCES/SFU class: Nov 3/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-79 (Audio cassette OBJ-4488)
      - Richard LeBourdie (Whispering Pine): Nov 18/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-80 (Audio cassette OBJ-4489)
      - Richard LeBourdais: Nov 18/95; tape II, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-81 (Audio cassette OBJ-4490)
      - Percy Casper (Bonaparte), SCES/SFU: Dec 1/95, 1995; F-251-6-1-0-5-82 (Audio cassette OBJ-4491)
    - Canadian Farmworkers Union interviews, 1983 - 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6
      - Interview: Calvin Sandborn (English; Vancouver, Oct 24/85; Farmworkers' movement; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4526)
      - Interviews: SideA- Terry Glavin; SideB- Mike Fleming; Farmworkers movement; Vancouver, Aug 12/85; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4527)
      - Interview: Kishan Walia (farm contractor); Vancouver; Punjabi; Farworkers movement; Oct 23/85; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4528)
      - Interview: Andy Sidhu, Canadian farm labour pool; Abbotsford, Oct 2/85, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4529)
      - Interview: Ted Horsting, farmer; Dec 6/85; Mission, B.C.; Dec 6/85; Farmworkers' movement; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4530)
      - Interviews with Raj Chouhan (Oct 21/83) and Judy Cavanagh (Nov 17/83), 1983; F-251-6-1-0-6-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-4531)
      - Interview: Mohinder Gill (Moe), farmer; Abbotsford; Oct 4/85; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-4532)
      - Interview: Major Gill (Punjabi); Dec 6/85; Mission; Farmworkers' movement; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-4533)
      - Interview: Harinder Mahil; Aug 30/85; Farmworkers movement; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-4534)
      - Interview with Art Kube, President, B.C. Federation of Labor; English Bay; Dec 18/85; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-4535)
        Side A is inaudible; Side B is blank.
      - Interview: Laurie White; White Rock; Sept 16/85; Farmworkers movement; by Sadhu Binning, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-4536)
      - Interview: Karen Dean; Vancouver; Sept 19/85; Farmworkers movement; by Sadhu Binning, F-251-6-1-0-6-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-4537)
      - Interview: Judy Cavanaugh (CFU); Sept 2/85; by Sukhwant Hundal, 1985; F-251-6-1-0-6-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-4538)
      - Interview with Raj Chouhan; Vancouver; June 16/90 at Hari's house; interview by Satya Sharma; Tape 1, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-4539)
      - Interview with Raj Chouhan; Vancouver; June 16/90 at Hari's house; interview by Satya Sharma; Tape 2, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-4492)
      - Interview with Sadhu Binning; Vancouver; May 29/90; by Satya, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-4493)
      - Interview with Sarwan Boal, President of CFU; Vancouver; May 23/90; by Satya, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-4494)
      - Pritam Singh Liddar Interview; Vancouver; June 1/90; by Satya, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-4495)
      - Interview with Harjinder Nijjar; Richmond; June 13/90; by Satya, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-4496)
      - Interview with Jwala Singh Grewal; Vancouver; May 29/90; by Satya, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-4497)
      - Judy Cavanaugh on CFU; Nov 3/90, 1990; F-251-6-1-0-6-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-4498)
    - Recordings of SFU lectures, 1980 - 1989; F-251-6-1-0-7
      - Parcham, vol. 1, [ca 1980]; F-251-6-1-0-7-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4499)
      - Medha Patkar, [ca 1980]; F-251-6-1-0-7-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4500)
      - M. Lebowitz, Feb 11/82; tape 1, 1982; F-251-6-1-0-7-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4501)
      - M. Lebowitz, Feb 11/82; tape 2, 1982; F-251-6-1-0-7-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4502)
      - M. Lebowitz, tape 3, 1982; F-251-6-1-0-7-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4503)
      - Special Lecture: Alavi, part 1/2; Jan 13/88, 1988; F-251-6-1-0-7-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-4504)
      - Special Lecture: Alavi, part 2/2; Jan 13/88, 1988; F-251-6-1-0-7-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-4505)
      - Tape 1: Dr. Saywell's lecture on China, Nov 23/89, SFU Harborside, 1989; F-251-6-1-0-7-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-4506)
      - Tape 2: Dr. Saywell's lecture on China, Nov 23/89, SFU Harborside, 1989; F-251-6-1-0-7-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-4507)
    - Interviews of Hari Sharma, 1991-2005; F-251-6-1-0-8
      - H. Sharma: My doctorate at Cornell; interview by Nandita Sharma, 1991; F-251-6-1-0-8-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4508)
      - Hari Sharma: Radio Interview on Babri Masjid, 1992; F-251-6-1-0-8-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4509)
      - H. Sharma: Radio Interview on Babri Masjid; CBC Commentary; Rafe Maer Show, 1993; F-251-6-1-0-8-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4510)
      - H. Sharma: Radio Interview on Babri Masjid; CBC Commentary; Rafe Maer Show (copy), 1993; F-251-6-1-0-8-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4511)
      - H. Sharma: Radio Interview on Babri Masjid; CBC Commentary; Rafe Maer Show (copy), 1993; F-251-6-1-0-8-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4512)
      - Aboriginal Youth Conference & Multiculturalism, 1994; F-251-6-1-0-8-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-4513)
      - C-FAX 1070 Victoria radio interview, 1996; F-251-6-1-0-8-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-4514)
      - Radio Interviews with H. Sharma (1996: VHP; 1997:Gurudwara), 1996-1997; F-251-6-1-0-8-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-4515)
      - CKNW interview (racism and tolerance in Vancouver), 1997; F-251-6-1-0-8-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-4516)
      - Hari Sharma: People's Conference Against Imperialism, globalization, 1997; F-251-6-1-0-8-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-4517)
      - Radio Interview, COOP Radio: Elections in India, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-8-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-4518)
      - Radio interviews: The Hindutava Bomb; On Racism with Alan Dutton, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-8-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-4519)
      - Radio interview: CKNW, Bill Good Show, The Hindutva Bomb, 1998; F-251-6-1-0-8-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-4520)